[Music]
[音乐]
这是一个令人愉悦的小机制
this is a pleasing little mechanism
被称为“千斤顶”的基地
非常高和狭窄，当你打开
this is a pleasing little mechanism
called the jack-in-the-box the base is
它的弹出窗口比底部宽，因此
很不寻常的一件，所以你这样做
called the jack-in-the-box the base is
very tall and narrow and when you open
需要一把尺子，一支铅笔和一把biro
得分是它的乐趣是
very tall and narrow and when you open
it the pop-up is wider than the base so
比身高还宽，所以当你来的时候
要测量你正在测量它
it the pop-up is wider than the base so
quite an unusual piece and so you do
这样的一半，你
用这种方式测量它始于
quite an unusual piece and so you do
need a ruler and a pencil and a biro to
一块总是对折
首先将其折叠成两半的弹出式窗口
need a ruler and a pencil and a biro to
score it with the pleasure of it is is
这样所有东西都是对称的
我们将以此来衡量
score it with the pleasure of it is is
wider than it is tall so when you come
我用笔来做，这样你就可以看到
然后我们把它的背面
wider than it is tall so when you come
to measuring you're measuring it on a
设计我要把尺子对付
中央折痕向下做一行
to measuring you're measuring it on a
half sheet like this and you're
那边有一行
顶部和第二个然后你
half sheet like this and you're
measuring it this way round start with
实际需要标记第三距离
下来，只需要标记
measuring it this way round start with
the piece folded in half always with
中心点，所以这是基本网格
你将要从
the piece folded in half always with
pop-ups you start with it folded in half
我们将在每侧都有标签
在这里和这里胶合到
pop-ups you start with it folded in half
that way everything is symmetrical so
背景，然后我们需要得分
这些折痕在这里是
that way everything is symmetrical so
we're going to be measuring from that
从这里开始，你得分像
那
we're going to be measuring from that
I'll do it with our pen so you can see
这也是这里，所以我们得分
所有这些对角线的对角线和
I'll do it with our pen so you can see
and then we'll make that the back of the
然后切掉，所以它将是一个
在这里停下来，所以我们远离了
and then we'll make that the back of the
design I'm putting the ruler up against
这是要粘贴的选项卡的行
它到页面
design I'm putting the ruler up against
the central crease and do one line down
在这方面，这些也是
手臂，所以我们只是沿着这些线
the central crease and do one line down
there one line down here one line across
头在这里
这是基本的形状，有折痕
there one line down here one line across
the top and the second one and then you
在中间，如果
将它对折，然后再对折
the top and the second one and then you
actually need to mark a third distance
那些对角线，所以你就像把它折叠起来
沿着对角线，这个你
actually need to mark a third distance
down just you just need to mark at the
沿对角线将其折叠，然后在
你来把它塑造成一切
down just you just need to mark at the
central point so this is the basic grid
动作简单轻松，就像这样
然后不要忘记这些侧面标签
central point so this is the basic grid
that you're going to be working from
不要以为我给我实际得分了
只是让他们快速浏览
that you're going to be working from
we're going to have tabs on each side
biro，所以它们折叠起来整齐干净
这是所有指导方针都在
we're going to have tabs on each side
here and here where it glues on to the
这个，所以我们要接受它
这样一来，所以我们需要实际
here and here where it glues on to the
background and then we need to score to
稍微折一下就可以了
很好，然后我在这里有一块
background and then we need to score to
make these creases here these are
这又是基本上
大小相等，是一半
make these creases here these are
starting from here you score up like
a4但我们要坚持下去
这样一来，您可以将其固定下来
starting from here you score up like
that
单位，我实际上要离开
我们可以在底部一点
that
and this one here as well so we score
稍后再玩，所以把两者都粘上
标签同时显示，因为我们
and this one here as well so we score
all these diagonals for diagonals and
粘平
我要把它贴在底部上方
all these diagonals for diagonals and
then cut it out so it's going to be a
边缘对齐中央折痕
弹出与中央对齐
then cut it out so it's going to be a
tab down here so we cut away from that
基础的折痕，所以这里
确保它工作正常
tab down here so we cut away from that
line that's the tab that's going to glue
现在您可以真正建立基础
甚至更小，您可以将其关闭，
line that's the tab that's going to glue
it to the page
看看外面的边缘有多近
这些离顶部有多近，修剪一下
it to the page
and on this side as well these are the
它下来，所以我可以看看那里我可以看到
在那边修剪所有的东西
and on this side as well these are the
arms so we just cut along those lines
离开，我也可以做整个事情
大约窄一厘米半英寸
the head up here
所以我也可以修剪一下
这个很小的卡，当您打开
here's the basic shape it's got a crease
现在出现了一个很大的盒子里的杰克
当它关闭时，您会看到
here's the basic shape it's got a crease
in the middle it's easier to actually if
手臂与脊柱齐平，所以您
不能在上方放置任何东西
in the middle it's easier to actually if
you fold it in half and then fold along
武器，但是你可以拥有任何你喜欢的东西
悬在他们下面，因为
you fold it in half and then fold along
those diagonals so you just fold it like
关闭，您在
手臂的底部和边缘
those diagonals so you just fold it like
that along the diagonal and this one you
卡，现在您实际上可以将其变成
站在底座上的弹出窗口，所以这是一个
that along the diagonal and this one you
fold it along the diagonal and then when
基础，我们只是要做一个基本的
直角折叠，这就是我去过的地方
fold it along the diagonal and then when
you come to push it into shape it all
将此空间留在底部a
厘米，所以我实际上
you come to push it into shape it all
moves nice and easy so it goes like that
得分，并使其成对
标签，然后像所有这些一样
moves nice and easy so it goes like that
and then don't forget these side tabs
只需要在下面剪掉那个角
所有折痕都匹配的地方，我会削减
and then don't forget these side tabs
don't think I scored those actually I'll
关闭这些，因此现在可以变成一个
在我推过的页面上翻折
don't think I scored those actually I'll
just give them a quick run over with the
在太远的地方，我们就是
要坐在上面
just give them a quick run over with the
biro so they fold nice and cleanly so
你只要把这些折叠起来
在这样的底座上，您需要在附近
biro so they fold nice and cleanly so
here it is all the guide lines are on
卡的正面，使其关闭
它会以这种方式折叠，我们
here it is all the guide lines are on
this one so we're going to take it on
只需确保它适合
在基本卡的角落和
this one so we're going to take it on
that way round so we need to actually
在这种情况下，将一侧粘起来并粘贴
那下来然后另一边
that way round so we need to actually
refold it slightly just so it all works
我将胶水都放在他们身上
正确，所以我们将其放置在
refold it slightly just so it all works
nicely and then I've got a piece here
基本都非常适合
一侧卡住的基卡关闭
nicely and then I've got a piece here
this again is it's the basically the
关闭找到它的位置的基础
想要好起来，有
this again is it's the basically the
same size as this it's a half sheet of
实际上，我们现在也弹出了
这里的背景不是很真实
same size as this it's a half sheet of
a4 but that we're going to stick it on
必要的，这样我们就可以减轻
你可以从这里切入
a4 but that we're going to stick it on
this way round you can stick it down
可能实际上想要更少，所以我们
可以拿工艺刀，只是
this way round you can stick it down
flat and I'm going to actually leave a
减少更多
在这里我可能应该这样做
flat and I'm going to actually leave a
little bit at the bottom that we can
在将其粘贴到底座和
另一边
little bit at the bottom that we can
play with later so put the glue on both
在那里，我们弹出框
[音乐]
play with later so put the glue on both
tabs at the same time because we're
[掌声]
您
tabs at the same time because we're
gluing it flat
[音乐]